- id: ckw-l01-142
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - パーセント
  hint: "noun/counter"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l01-351
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ページ
  hint: "noun/counter"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l01-420
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - センター
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l01-549
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - サービス
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l01-557
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - システム
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l01-574
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - メートル
  hint: "noun/counter"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l01-589
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - テレビ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l01-592
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - メール
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l01-709
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - データ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l01-875
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ポイント
  hint: "noun/counter"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l01-888
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ホーム
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l01-908
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ホテル
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l01-935
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ブログ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l01-940
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - クリック
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l01-949
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - グループ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []
